[{"id": "5909cfedbb53d1af658864f7", "question": "What was the name of the toy store in the film \"Home Alone 2\"?", "answer": "Duncan\u2019s Toy Chest", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b779", "question": "How many holes are there in a standard Ritz cracker?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be22", "question": "In what country was actor Rick Fox born?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c366", "question": "What shape is the piston in a \"Wankel\" engine?", "answer": "Triangular", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c873", "question": "A tetragon is geometric shape that has how many sides?", "answer": "Four", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0c1", "question": "Which car manufacturer's name translates from Latin as \"to roll\"?", "answer": "Volvo", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b021", "question": "Who was U.S. President when electricity was installed in the White House, in 1891?", "answer": "Benjamin Harrison", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffa551cc73aa70ea0b70b21", "question": "Which district in central Tokyo is particularly famous for its electronics?", "answer": "Akihabara", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a411", "question": "A person from North Carolina is properly known as a what?", "answer": "North Carolinian", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5989ae68cb8751d53e7d7615", "question": "The dance called the \"Maxixe\" is also known by what name?", "answer": "Brazilian Tango", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe76b93eec85e375820b2c4", "question": "Where can you hike Hadrian\u2019s wall?", "answer": "England", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a875", "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named \"Haight Street\"?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1f1", "question": "Who played the lead female in the 1956 film \"Meet Me in Las Vegas\"?", "answer": "Cyd Charisse", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9f4", "question": "What animal rests in a form?", "answer": "The hare", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339af4", "question": "What TV series, which ran from 2004 thru 2008, was a spin-off from \"The Practice\"?", "answer": "Boston Legal", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601debe96b1208747aa7e9d7", "question": "Which famous entrepreneur is credited with inventing the weekend?", "answer": "Henry Ford", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59cdb40365ff7d326b622a83", "question": "What year was Budweiser first introduced?", "answer": "1876", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ae8641c7f28483af1e7fdcd", "question": "In which year did India gain its independence from the United Kingdom?", "answer": "1947", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133998b", "question": "What was the name of the main police detective played by Jack Webb on the TV show \"Dragnet\"?", "answer": "Joe Friday", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b197", "question": "What year was Cable News Network, or CNN,  launched?", "answer": "1980", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d36", "question": "Who's responsible for \"The Ballad of Reading Gaol\"?", "answer": "Oscar Wilde", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391fe", "question": "In which movie did Eddie Murphy play a character named Prince Akeem?", "answer": "Coming to America", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5d1", "question": "What company makes Reese's Peanut Butter Cups?", "answer": "The Hershey Company", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a833", "question": "Because it entered the union in 1876, what western US state is nicknamed \"The Centennial State\"?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bd7", "question": "Pax is the Roman god of what?", "answer": "Peace", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a787", "question": "What important crop is the Rhine Valley in Germany known for growing?", "answer": "Grapes", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf89", "question": "Bourbon, sugar, mint and water make up which type of cocktail?", "answer": "Mint Julep", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ec", "question": "What is the technical name of the pound sign?", "answer": "Octothorpe", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2b1", "question": "What US president returned the US controlled Panama Canal Zone to Panama?", "answer": "Jimmy Carter", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9ca", "question": "The \"Dreamcatcher\" was invented by which Native America group?", "answer": "Ojibwe", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6010c5840775fa611bce67c8", "question": "What is the only spice native to all 48 contiguous U.S. states?", "answer": "Sumac -- The tangy, lemon-flavored spice comes from the edible red berries of a small tree which are crushed to create the spice.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5eb", "question": "In which country is Angel Falls located?", "answer": "Venezuela", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb15", "question": "What city was home to the NBA's Jazz before moving to Utah?", "answer": "New Orleans", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac52", "question": "What was the first animal sent up to outer space?", "answer": "Dog", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58c8a63b90aac110e416707c", "question": "What fruit oil is added to tea to create Earl Grey tea?", "answer": "Bergamot", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a2f", "question": "What country was the birthplace of two of the Three Tenors?", "answer": "Spain", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5e94cfb75ea27d7a1303aed0", "question": "Which letter represents Potassium on the Periodic Table of Elements?", "answer": "K", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399aa", "question": "What 1990 John Hughes move was hyped as \"a family comedy, without the family\"?", "answer": "Home Alone", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133975b", "question": "Who plays the last man on Earth in I Am Legend?", "answer": "Will Smith", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa90", "question": "Roseau is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Dominica", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339450", "question": "How did the children die in the 2001 movie \"The Others\"?", "answer": "Suffocation", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a43", "question": "In which country is the city Aachen located?", "answer": "Germany", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fecda46ec223966ae8f88e7", "question": "What was the first movie by Pixar to receive a rating higher than G in the United States?", "answer": "The Incredibles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5eb736465e259d786908732b", "question": "What was the name of the US Navy boat that had the nickname \"Old Ironsides\"?", "answer": "USS Constitution", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339223", "question": "What is the name of Futurama's first episode aired in 1999?", "answer": "Space Pilot 3000", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdca", "question": "What off-road endurance race is named after the African capital where it usually ends?", "answer": "The Dakar Rally", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9d6", "question": "What large red flower is the floral emblem of New South Wales?", "answer": "Waratah", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6002433f4be4723ccac22193", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"Lolita\"?", "answer": "Russian-American author Vladimir Nabokov", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339814", "question": "\"Take the A Train\" was the signature tune of whose band?", "answer": "Duke Ellington", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a27920565ad31a57c7ac", "question": "What museum is home to the oldest surviving piano?", "answer": "The Met", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b55b", "question": "What is the term used for the science of growing an apple?", "answer": "Pomology", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f8a", "question": "What actress earned an Oscar nomination for her first screen appearance in \"Maria Full of Grace\"?", "answer": "Catalina Sandino Moreno", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bad", "question": "How many nights are there in \"Arabian Nights\"?", "answer": "1001", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338be9", "question": "Which instrument does the Leader of an orchestra play?", "answer": "Violin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339017", "question": "Shu was an Egyptian God of what?", "answer": "The Air", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bff", "question": "What movie does the line \"Nobody puts Baby in the corner\" hails form?", "answer": "Dirty Dancing", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b06c", "question": "During the mid-1800\u2019s, what was the principal cargo aboard Mississippi River Steamboats?", "answer": "Cotton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6996a20565ad31a57c746", "question": "In the Bible, who sold his birthright because he was hungry?", "answer": "Esau", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600cc8e76de0eb824d405300", "question": "Which borough has New York City's only surf beach?", "answer": "Queens -- Rockaway Beach, just a subway ride away from Manhattan, is the only surf-able beach in NYC limits.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58dba4ea874c93a3298b214a", "question": "What does Mount Snowdon's Welsh name \"Yr Wyddfe\" roughly translate to?", "answer": "The tumulus, or the barrow", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ebf", "question": "What does Bruce Springsteen have tucked in his back pocket on the cover of \"Born in the USA\"?", "answer": "A baseball cap", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339465", "question": "Who wrote the movie \"Natural Born Killers\"?", "answer": "Quentin Tarantino", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338941", "question": "What creatures in \"The Lord of the Rings\" are referred to as goblins in the book \"The Hobbit\"?", "answer": "Orcs", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ad7", "question": "What \"Saturday Night Live\" castmember played Sean Connery in their Celebrity Jeopardy skits?", "answer": "Darrell Hammond", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ccf7bb0b37b32637bdc44c6", "question": "In what year was the language learning site/app Duolingo launched?", "answer": "2011", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c18b", "question": "Vinnie Jones was associated with which sport?", "answer": "Soccer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff51cecff04d658268c931f", "question": "What famous general was once attacked by rabbits?", "answer": "Napoleon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a179", "question": "Which actor was \"The Postman\"?", "answer": "Kevin Costner", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ad7ea43b24f84e0b9f9ffd2", "question": "What is a figure with eight equal sides called?", "answer": "Regular Octagon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b602", "question": "The cover of what band's 1977 album \"Animals\" depicts a large, inflatable pig flying over London's Battersea Power Station?", "answer": "Pink Floyd", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8d0", "question": "What baseball team suffered from the \"Curse of the Bambino\"?", "answer": "Boston Red Sox", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad88", "question": "Who reigned as Queen of England for only 9 days?", "answer": "Lady Jane Grey", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ea6", "question": "In what comic strip would you find siblings Zoe, Hammy and Wren?", "answer": "Baby Blues", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2f7", "question": "What is believed to be created when a star collapses?", "answer": "A black hole", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fef5e296ce05a3942286e30", "question": "Which horror movie\u2019s sequel has the tagline, \"They\u2019re back\"?", "answer": "\"Poltergeist\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4bc", "question": "Deuteranopia is one of the most common varieties of what condition?", "answer": "Color Blindness", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd660a8a5bfecdd737e0836", "question": "What did \"RMS\" in RMS Titanic stand for?", "answer": "Royal Mail Ship", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c22e", "question": "Eclairs are said to have originated in which country?", "answer": "France", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cb5", "question": "What was the better-known name of Margareta Zelle, exotic dancer?", "answer": "Mata Hari", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600cc14d6de0eb824d4052de", "question": "In what three places did the Republic of Texas maintain legations?", "answer": "They were located at Pickering Place, London, England, Washington, D.C. and 1 Place Vendome, Paris, France.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe0e439fcbed638185eaa26", "question": "What is the most visited attraction in New York City?", "answer": "The Metropolitan Museum of Art", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58f5658333a95c66dc4fe758", "question": "Which number system uses only the symbols 1 and 0?", "answer": "The binary system", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e5f0bafd274615ecf514530", "question": "What brand of melty cheese was first introduced to the mass market in 1928?", "answer": "Velveeta", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fede5b66ce05a3942286def", "question": "Which American television sitcom is about a witch who marries an ordinary man and lives as a suburban housewife?", "answer": "\"Bewitched\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cc8", "question": "Who had a surprise cameo as \"Agent M\" in \"Men in Black II\"?", "answer": "Michael Jackson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339429", "question": "Who is \"The Jerk\"?", "answer": "Steve Martin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff5176dff04d658268c92fb", "question": "What was traditionally painted on the eastern side of a sarcophagus?", "answer": "Eyes (The eastern side was often painted with eyes because it was believed that the deceased could still watch the rising sun.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6ec", "question": "The cerebrum is the largest part of what organ?", "answer": "The brain", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe3e59c38e4e5d4832e6305", "question": "Who were the Tuskegee Airmen?", "answer": "African-American fighter pilots who fought during World War II", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015f76efe83fe1f2a824c21", "question": "A three-day celebration triduum that involves; Halloween, All Saints Day, and All Souls Day can be referred to as?", "answer": "Allhallowtide, which can also be called Allsaintstide or Hallowtide.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fecda82ec223966ae8f88e9", "question": "What film features a fight scene in which Bruce Lee breaks Jackie Chan's neck?", "answer": "Enter the Dragon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391b3", "question": "Which movie was the first feature film made entirely in CGI?", "answer": "Toy Story", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a4a979661d1b4d384d5d686", "question": "In the world of tennis, who was the first to win all four Grand Slams in the same year?", "answer": "Don Budge", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59e6bd30fb6c85e9e634ff64", "question": "Who won the World Series in 1987?", "answer": "Minnesota Twins", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b37b", "question": "Who conquered the Matterhorn in 1865?", "answer": "Edward Whymper", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd66479a5bfecdd737e0855", "question": "Who was the first US president to be heard on the radio?", "answer": "Warren Harding", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae22", "question": "What are the four permanent, non-US members of the United Nations Security Council?", "answer": "China, France, Russia, United Kingdom", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8f2", "question": "Where would you find Olympus Mons?", "answer": "Mars", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a231", "question": "With which instrument is jazz musician Charlie Mingus principally associated?", "answer": "Double Bass", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388af", "question": "What kind of a dog is Marmaduke?", "answer": "A Great Dane", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae90", "question": "Which US president resided at the Hermitage, a plantation in Tennessee?", "answer": "Andrew Jackson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f62", "question": "In the children's book \"Feyesper and the Rogue Kite\", what animal is Feyesper based on?", "answer": "Pink fairy armadillo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c50b", "question": "Approximately how many times does a person blink in a day?", "answer": "20,000", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe65d3e1f3c0ead6880d619", "question": "What Enron CEO took the company to financial disaster?", "answer": "Kenneth Lay", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59db76db0ab2c8f322317fe8", "question": "In which ocean would you find the Republic of Seychelles?", "answer": "Indian Ocean", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58d47509f8e329de4f8778a3", "question": "What is the capital of Venezuela?", "answer": "Caracas", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab09", "question": "What is the capital of the Tonga?", "answer": "Nuku'alofa", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cf7", "question": "What is the best known artificial international language?", "answer": "Esperanto", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5f3052145aa2bc17b61b2ac8", "question": "Chisinau is the capital of what country?", "answer": "Moldova", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397e6", "question": "From which US state does Jerry Hall come?", "answer": "Texas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ef", "question": "In the book \"Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows\" what does the acronym RAB stand for?", "answer": "Regulus A. Black", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdfb83e003d27d341092bbc", "question": "Which country has the most embassies abroad?", "answer": "USA", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e8c", "question": "What future celebrity made an appearance as Molly in \"Home Alone 3\"?", "answer": "Scarlett Johansson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeb6", "question": "Who was married to Princess Anne in 1992?", "answer": "Tim Lawrence", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff3c2f64f032c0db195b488", "question": "What charter did a group of English barons force King John to sign in 1215 at Runnymede?", "answer": "Magna Carta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b831", "question": "What city is home to Amazon.com's headquarters?", "answer": "Seattle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b25a", "question": "Which amendment to the US Constitution deals with the income tax?", "answer": "Sixteenth", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d07", "question": "Whose sidekick was named Garth Algar?", "answer": "Wayne Campbell", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b594", "question": "When was the game \"Scrabble\" first released?", "answer": "1948", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a683", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the \"Treasure State\"?", "answer": "Montana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59636f8f967692ea851899b6", "question": "In what game do you have the greatest chance of landing on Illinois Avenue?", "answer": "Monopoly", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c54e", "question": "What digit does not exist in Roman Numerals?", "answer": "Zero", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600f74c4a9e54d890926f6ff", "question": "In June in Wyoming, it is illegal to take a picture of what?", "answer": "A rabbit", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a190", "question": "Paul Stanley is the co-singer for which Rock-N-Roll band?", "answer": "Kiss", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60078bd40eee65b76b9f266d", "question": "What was the name of the first English child born in the Americas?", "answer": "Virginia Dare (She was born August 18, 1587 in\u00a0Roanoke Colony.  She and about 120 settlers mysteriously disappeared.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bda7", "question": "Whose emblem came from a sketch Lamar Hunt drew on a napkin in 1963?", "answer": "The Kansas City Chiefs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e38d000f6c8a670a7957c55", "question": "What is the name of the first single by the Korean girl-group \"Red Velvet\"?", "answer": "Happiness", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ba4", "question": "Which state is located between Wisconsin and North Dakota?", "answer": "Minnesota", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339699", "question": "Which movie gave us the line \"You talkin' to me?\"", "answer": "Taxi Driver", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe69fe920565ad31a57c792", "question": "What is the oldest-known epic tale?", "answer": "\"Epic of Gilgamesh\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "596dfa93cf3977a46e7ce447", "question": "The Statue of Liberty was a gift resulting from the diplomatic relationship between the United States and what country?", "answer": "France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b795", "question": "Christmas caroling began as what old English custom?", "answer": "Wassailing", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6ac", "question": "How many watts make a kilowatt?", "answer": "1000", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58f169ddf7c52aae91cc07d5", "question": "Who played the role of \"Hawkeye\" in the TV show \"M*A*S*H\"?", "answer": "Alan Alda", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab8e", "question": "What country shares a border with Cambodia to the northeast?", "answer": "Laos", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339977", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", Lenny has a master's degree in what field?", "answer": "Nuclear Physics", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea375bff048f679a45ab17", "question": "What is the second derivative of displacement?", "answer": "Instantaneous Acceleration", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6db", "question": "A cygnet is the name for a newly hatched or baby what?", "answer": "Swan", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c407", "question": "Who is typically credited with inventing the first DC motor in 1837?", "answer": "Thomas Davenport", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd96c5a23c87fd04dd15e23", "question": "Which president appeared on a U.S. coin while he was still alive?", "answer": "Calvin Coolidge", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7d564877e98cb97778a64", "question": "What actor played the school principal in E.T., only to have his scene cut when Spielberg decided that his presence would be too distracting?", "answer": "Harrison Ford", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0aa", "question": "What Nazi Field Marshall was known as \"The Desert Fox\"?", "answer": "Erwin Rommel", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b94", "question": "On \"The Beverly Hillbillies\" TV show, what was the name of Jethro's mother?", "answer": "Pearl Bodine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc1e", "question": "What year was the Rubik's Cube invented?", "answer": "1974", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a52c", "question": "The mouth of the Mississippi River is located in which state?", "answer": "Louisiana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339440", "question": "Why is Bob Harris in Tokyo in the movie \"Lost in Translation\"?", "answer": "To film a whiskey commercial", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4dc", "question": "What city is graced with Michelangelo's David?", "answer": "Florence", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5cefc199948005ec986edce6", "question": "What powers Iron Man's suit?", "answer": "Arc reactor", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6014c47efbde8045e484669c", "question": "What are the only large cats that roar together as a group?", "answer": "Lions -- Used to mark territories, a pride of lions can be heard from 5 miles away.  Even the young cubs will join in the roaring.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b36", "question": "What is Dorothy's last name in \"The Wonderful Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer": "Gale", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abba", "question": "What US state is also known as The Golden State?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339983", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what was the name of Barney's self-documentary?", "answer": "Puke-a-hontas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133905c", "question": "Who was poet Sylvia Plath married to?", "answer": "Ted Hughes", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339059", "question": "Which author wrote \"The Duncton Chronicles\"?", "answer": "William Horwood", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339962", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what nickname did Milhouse give himself?", "answer": "Thrillhouse", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b119", "question": "What Spanish explorer is credited with discovering the Pacific Ocean?", "answer": "Balboa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391aa", "question": "Who played James Bond in the 1971 film \"Diamonds Are Forever\"?", "answer": "Sean Connery", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e05", "question": "What movie was partially inspired by Jean Shepherd's unpublished story \"Flick's Tongue\"?", "answer": "A Christmas Story", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c99a", "question": "In which constellation are the Seven Sisters located?", "answer": "Taurus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133980b", "question": "Which ballad by the band Poison is about a Vietnam veteran and the homeless?", "answer": "Something To Believe In", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "596dfdb79616e6c6d4eba4f8", "question": "On the hit show \"Seinfeld\" what was Kramer's first name? ", "answer": "Cosmo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a476", "question": "What African country was formerly known as Northern Rhodesia?", "answer": "Zambia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5977432a284458f1d7854427", "question": "Albert Einstein was offered the position of prime minister of what country?", "answer": "Israel", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5a25ef516682715b82711cd6", "question": "What year did the Mayflower transport the first English Puritans to the New World?", "answer": "1620", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd2d9b02596a59cbdfbd3c9", "question": "What was the first crime Billy the Kid was arrested for?", "answer": "Stealing clothes", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea3d1fff048f679a45ab48", "question": "A medical condition that has been caused by a physician or medical treatment is described as what?", "answer": "Iatrogenic", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ad7e7e0b24f84e0b9f9ffc0", "question": "Which state surrounds the Australian Capital Territory?", "answer": "New South Wales", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fed2bbaec223966ae8f8911", "question": "What is the name of the smelly green ghost in \"Ghostbusters\"?", "answer": "Slimer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fefbe906ce05a3942286ef3", "question": "Who recorded the song \"Lyin' Eyes\"?", "answer": "Eagles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6017380944491cbd7c5a1793", "question": "During World War II, prisoners wearing an uninverted red triangle in a concentration camp signified the prisoners were what?", "answer": "An enemy\u00a0POW, a spy or traitor, a military\u00a0deserter\u00a0or a military criminal.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a3b", "question": "The Stephen Sondheim Broadway musical \"Sunday in the Park with George\" was based on a painting by what artist?", "answer": "Georges Seurat", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd6a00d6c0f9723ab15cb32", "question": "What year was the first black hole discovered?", "answer": "1971", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58bb333de368446ca7bd6842", "question": "Who was the Phillips screw design named after?", "answer": "Henry F. Phillips", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600f6f36a9e54d890926f6cf", "question": "Which U.S. state has an official state cookie called biscochito?", "answer": "New Mexico -- Brought to the\u00a0region by 16th-century Spanish colonists, it is a shortbread cookie flavored with cinnamon and anise.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133924e", "question": "Who plays Will Turner in the movie \"Pirates of the Caribbean\"?", "answer": "Orlando Bloom", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bc5", "question": "David Bowie's \"Let's Dance\" album was released in what year?", "answer": "1983", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea3985ff048f679a45ab28", "question": "What is the smallest organ in the human body?", "answer": "Pineal gland", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59675ca32b59efe0e9417e95", "question": "The dragonfly has six legs but rarely does what?", "answer": "Walk", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4df", "question": "What fruit comes in Damson and Mirabelle variety?", "answer": "Plums", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d92", "question": "What original literary work was the movie \"Ossessione\" based on?", "answer": "The Postman Always Rings Twice", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e81", "question": "During what war was the novel \"Richard III\" set?", "answer": "Wars of the Roses", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f60", "question": "Which 1966 story, by Philip K. Dick, served as the basis for the 1990 movie \"Total Recall\"?", "answer": "We Can Remember It for You Wholesale", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe4eed806d333868d34d776", "question": "Where did the croissant originate?", "answer": "Austria", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338de0", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"safari\"?", "answer": "Arabic", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a00e", "question": "Whose Atlantic recordings are collected in a set called \"Queen of Soul\"?", "answer": "Aretha Franklin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5990f950fa5fdd6dd25324f6", "question": "What name is given to animals which only eat plants?", "answer": "Herbivores", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58ab15e4baab681b0929217f", "question": "What was the world\u2019s first mass-produced car to feature an all-aluminium body?", "answer": "Honda NSX", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fefbf806ce05a3942286f00", "question": "In the television series \"Magnum P.I.\", Magnum often wore a ball cap for which sport's team?", "answer": "Detroit Tigers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391c8", "question": "What is James Dean's middle name?", "answer": "Byron", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b40", "question": "Which items are melting in Salvador Dali's painting \"The Persistence of Memory\"?", "answer": "Watches", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ab3", "question": "\"Little Bastard\" was the nickname given to the Porsche 550 Spyder that killed what acting icon in a crash?", "answer": "James Dean", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1cc", "question": "Whose execution caused the famed Spanish Armada to sail against England?", "answer": "Mary, Queen of Scots'", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1b2", "question": "Who played the male starring role in 1967 film \"The Graduate\"?", "answer": "Dustin Hoffman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b530", "question": "What color is bianco wine?", "answer": "White", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3b9", "question": "What do most lobsters and crayfish do with their shell after it has molted?", "answer": "Eat it", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5cefc114948005ec986edce3", "question": "Who is the tenth member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Chuu", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a69e", "question": "What two lakes meet at the Straits of Mackinac?", "answer": "Lake Michigan and Lake Huron", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fefc4b36ce05a3942286f35", "question": "Who replaced Curly of the Three Stooges after he had a stroke in 1946?", "answer": "Shemp Howard", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339259", "question": "What actor originated the role of Inspector Clouseau?", "answer": "Peter Sellers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd2d0442596a59cbdfbd379", "question": "Who said, \"When I do good, I feel good. When I do bad, I feel bad. That's my religion\"?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c956", "question": "Approximately how many kilometres is an Astronomical Unit?", "answer": "150 million", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133900d", "question": "What fruit was referred to as \"Golden Apple\" in Greek myth?", "answer": "Apricot", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a53b", "question": "What US city is nicknamed the \"Motor City\"?", "answer": "Detroit", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1b4", "question": "Canadian Prime Minister Lester Pearson won the Nobel Peace Prize for defusing what world crisis?", "answer": "The Suez Crisis", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7f4", "question": "What Georgia city was Jimmy Carter's hometown?", "answer": "Plains", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf65", "question": "What is Wales' national dish called?", "answer": "Cawl", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c793", "question": "What part of the cheetah does not have any spots?", "answer": "The belly", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6014c99afbde8045e48466f0", "question": "How many plates make up the Earth's crust?", "answer": "15 -- The Earth's crust is made up with 7 major and 8 minor plates.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4d0", "question": "What does a \u201cseismograph\u201d measure?", "answer": "Motions of the ground", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe69bed20565ad31a57c765", "question": "Who was the first U.S. senator to be elected president?", "answer": "James Monroe", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d74", "question": "What classic novel's subtitle is \"There and Back Again\"?", "answer": "The Hobbit", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aff0", "question": "Which US president delivered the Gettysburg Address?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f12", "question": "What author created Narnia?", "answer": "C. S. Lewis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fed2b94ec223966ae8f890e", "question": "What film bankrupted Carolco Pictures?", "answer": "\"Cutthroat Island\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a666", "question": "What US city is home to the International UFO Museum and Research Center?", "answer": "Roswell", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b3234fbbf195a31e15d73aa", "question": "Which artist starred in the title role of the film \"Merry Christmas, Mr. Lawrence\"?", "answer": "David Bowie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b614", "question": "First marketed in 1952, Pream was a brand of instant what?", "answer": "Creamer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d54", "question": "What year saw the release of the first Harry Potter book?", "answer": "1997", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff516cfff04d658268c92f5", "question": "Who came up with \"The Allegory of the Cave\"?", "answer": "Plato", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133923e", "question": "What superhero is known as the \"Caped Crusader\"?", "answer": "Batman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdfbaa8003d27d341092bc4", "question": "What are Easter Island's famous statues called?", "answer": "Moai", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c022", "question": "What year was fashion designer Gianni Versace killed?", "answer": "1997", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b187", "question": "Who was US President Ronald Reagan's first wife?", "answer": "Jane Wyman", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a4a995e61d1b4d384d5d699", "question": "Who played the role of Thad Greenwood in the TV show \"Gunsmoke\"?", "answer": "Roger Ewing", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dce", "question": "What two Rocky III costars won the final match of the very first WrestleMania?", "answer": "Mr. T and Hulk Hogan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5b2", "question": "Which state is home to the oceanside city Myrtle Beach?", "answer": "South Carolina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ae862f37f28483af1e7fdc8", "question": "What country did Hawaiian pizza come from?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc0d", "question": "What year did Wayne Gretzky retire from his professional hockey career?", "answer": "1999", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392a7", "question": "Who provided the voice for Mickey Mouse from 1928 to 1946?", "answer": "Walt Disney", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a590", "question": "What U.S. state is proud to call itself \"the Beaver State\"?", "answer": "Oregon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6008dd97f4f3bc4a292f8622", "question": "\"Operation Overlord\" was the code name for the invasion of what country during World War II?", "answer": "German-occupied France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "601b490049076251badbeaaa", "question": "The Treaty of Ghent was the peace treaty that ended which war?", "answer": "War of 1812", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b539", "question": "What non-alcoholic syrup is made from pomegranate juice?", "answer": "Grenadine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba5e", "question": "What song, first used by FDR, has since become the unofficial theme song of the US Democratic party?", "answer": "Happy Days Are Here Again", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ab99c4821a8909e5c332d34", "question": "Who played Franz Liszt in the 1975 film \"Lisztomania\"?", "answer": "Roger Daltrey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af0d", "question": "What nickname was given to General Thomas J. Jackson during the Civil War?", "answer": "\"Stonewall\" Jackson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac79", "question": "During which American period did stock car racing gain most of its popularity?", "answer": "The Prohibition", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fefc5776ce05a3942286f3f", "question": "What Scottish poet\u2019s works inspired the book titles Of Mice and Men and Catcher in the Rye?", "answer": "Robert Burns", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffa54bdc73aa70ea0b70b1e", "question": "Which country (and it's territories) cover the most time zones?", "answer": "France and its eight territories cover 12 time zones.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be16", "question": "The sousaphone is a marching-band version of what symphony instrument?", "answer": "The tuba", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b474", "question": "What year did Andre and Edouard Michelin first publish the \"Michelin Guide\"?", "answer": "1900", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015eaccfe83fe1f2a824bf5", "question": "What does the color blue represent in the American flag?", "answer": "Blue symbolizes vigilance, perseverance and justice.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5921fed3a4edfd43a087add1", "question": "What currency was used in the Netherlands before the introduction of the Euro?", "answer": "Guilders", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe37af80ada16518afdc05e", "question": "What action did the U.S. take along with Great Britain and Australia after Japan seized Indochina?", "answer": "They formed a trade embargo that cut off 90% of Japan's oil supply", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b06e", "question": "What was the infamous pseudonym of William Bonney?", "answer": "Billy the Kid", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392f4", "question": "In the movie \"Jurassic Park\", what animal was used to lure the T-Rex?", "answer": "A goat", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600242004be4723ccac22180", "question": "Which Irish poet, born in 1865, was instrumental in the founding of the Abbey Theatre in Dublin?", "answer": "William Butler Yeats", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c989", "question": "Macrophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Long waits", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b40", "question": "How many episodes of \"The Bob Newhart Show\" were made?", "answer": "142", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd11", "question": "What was the original brand of cereal whose mascot was Wendell?", "answer": "Cinnamon Toast Crunch", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58b8ce4794b094db915830a6", "question": "The city of Acapulco is located in which Mexican state?", "answer": "Guerrero", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339684", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", who shot Mr. Burns?", "answer": "Maggie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1cb", "question": "Oslo's Holocaust research center is the former home of what firing squad victim?", "answer": "Vidkun Quisling", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c0f", "question": "What is comedian Jon Stewart's full birth name?", "answer": "Jonathan Stuart Leibowitz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f61", "question": "Eric Arthur Blair was better known by what pen name?", "answer": "George Orwell", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fede1eb6ce05a3942286dc8", "question": "In \"Frosty the Snowman\", what are Frosty's eyes made of?", "answer": "Coal", "category": "entertainment"}]